{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685235677","data":{"timestamp":" 947685235677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" b5693859-c580-4fda-a861-26cefc5a730a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685244957","data":{"timestamp":" 947685244957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685245190","data":{"timestamp":" 947685245190"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685246168","data":{"timestamp":" 947685246168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685247450","data":{"timestamp":" 947685247450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685250375","data":{"timestamp":" 947685250375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685251230","data":{"timestamp":" 947685251229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685251550","data":{"timestamp":" 947685251549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685252797","data":{"timestamp":" 947685252796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685256376","data":{"timestamp":" 947685256375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685257371","data":{"timestamp":" 947685257370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685257633","data":{"timestamp":" 947685257632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685258588","data":{"timestamp":" 947685258587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685261481","data":{"timestamp":" 947685261481"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685262513","data":{"timestamp":" 947685262513"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685262986","data":{"timestamp":" 947685262986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685267504","data":{"timestamp":" 947685267503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685267562","data":{"timestamp":" 947685267562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" a7cf3a05-aef0-4877-bc07-671e439abe1d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685298331","data":{"timestamp":" 947685298330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685301288","data":{"timestamp":" 947685301288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" CHUMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685304479","data":{"timestamp":" 947685304479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685310820","data":{"timestamp":" 947685310820"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685315440","data":{"timestamp":" 947685315440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685317442","data":{"timestamp":" 947685317442"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685320810","data":{"timestamp":" 947685320810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685330227","data":{"timestamp":" 947685330227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi ninapenda kucheza na rafiki yangu Chuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685332953","data":{"timestamp":" 947685332953"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685336370","data":{"timestamp":" 947685336370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685340526","data":{"timestamp":" 947685340526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685350027","data":{"timestamp":" 947685350027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAPENDANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685357987","data":{"timestamp":" 947685357987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na Chuma tunapendana sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685361269","data":{"timestamp":" 947685361269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKITUMWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685363586","data":{"timestamp":" 947685363586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685366128","data":{"timestamp":" 947685366128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukitumwa tunaenda pamoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685368080","data":{"timestamp":" 947685368080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685368284","data":{"timestamp":" 947685368283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685369784","data":{"timestamp":" 947685369784"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685384563","data":{"timestamp":" 947685384563"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILITUMWA"," userResponse":" NILITUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685386044","data":{"timestamp":" 947685386044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUKANI"," userResponse":" DUKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685386048","data":{"timestamp":" 947685386048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685388166","data":{"timestamp":" 947685388165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" CHUMVI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685390936","data":{"timestamp":" 947685390936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685392426","data":{"timestamp":" 947685392425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685393112","data":{"timestamp":" 947685393112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685394038","data":{"timestamp":" 947685394037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" START_YANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685395507","data":{"timestamp":" 947685395507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685396905","data":{"timestamp":" 947685396904"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NIKANUNUE"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685399841","data":{"timestamp":" 947685399840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKANUNUE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685401930","data":{"timestamp":" 947685401930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUMVI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685404523","data":{"timestamp":" 947685404523"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685410248","data":{"timestamp":" 947685410247"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_48","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685414583","data":{"timestamp":" 947685414583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685414673","data":{"timestamp":" 947685414673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" ea08dd66-02b6-4b4f-ba6d-9535f43dc89b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_48"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja nilitumwa dukani na nyanya yangu nikanunue chumvi na mafuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAFUTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685443721","data":{"timestamp":" 947685443721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" fa91f5b9-1409-478e-8af0-8acd8a24c334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685461897","data":{"timestamp":" 947685461897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" fa91f5b9-1409-478e-8af0-8acd8a24c334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685478527","data":{"timestamp":" 947685478527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" fa91f5b9-1409-478e-8af0-8acd8a24c334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685506471","data":{"timestamp":" 947685506471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" fa91f5b9-1409-478e-8af0-8acd8a24c334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685519076","data":{"timestamp":" 947685519076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" fa91f5b9-1409-478e-8af0-8acd8a24c334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685531525","data":{"timestamp":" 947685531525"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" fa91f5b9-1409-478e-8af0-8acd8a24c334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685567747","data":{"timestamp":" 947685567747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" fa91f5b9-1409-478e-8af0-8acd8a24c334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+0"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685577008","data":{"timestamp":" 947685577008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" fa91f5b9-1409-478e-8af0-8acd8a24c334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+0"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685591308","data":{"timestamp":" 947685591307"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" fa91f5b9-1409-478e-8af0-8acd8a24c334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_2+0"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685607048","data":{"timestamp":" 947685607047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" de2e08c4-ae5c-4d82-a9cd-6dead19e0797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685608507","data":{"timestamp":" 947685608507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" de2e08c4-ae5c-4d82-a9cd-6dead19e0797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685615507","data":{"timestamp":" 947685615507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" de2e08c4-ae5c-4d82-a9cd-6dead19e0797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685615668","data":{"timestamp":" 947685615668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" de2e08c4-ae5c-4d82-a9cd-6dead19e0797"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_50"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye msitu wa Miwa paliishi tumbili aliyekuwa na huzuni sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685659875","data":{"timestamp":" 947685659874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685660104","data":{"timestamp":" 947685660104"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685661081","data":{"timestamp":" 947685661080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685662365","data":{"timestamp":" 947685662364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685665289","data":{"timestamp":" 947685665288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685666158","data":{"timestamp":" 947685666154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685666479","data":{"timestamp":" 947685666478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685667726","data":{"timestamp":" 947685667725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685671291","data":{"timestamp":" 947685671290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685672286","data":{"timestamp":" 947685672286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685672550","data":{"timestamp":" 947685672550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685673509","data":{"timestamp":" 947685673509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685676409","data":{"timestamp":" 947685676409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685677454","data":{"timestamp":" 947685677454"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685677938","data":{"timestamp":" 947685677937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685682492","data":{"timestamp":" 947685682491"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685682598","data":{"timestamp":" 947685682597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947685704884","data":{"timestamp":" 947685704884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_165341"," gameId":" 02b2990f-e6e2-4d9e-8abc-f4582e0c4005"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}